

Profile

In the last years I have acquired professional experience in .NET and associated technologies.

I have worked mainly as FullStack developer (mainly Angular and .NET), however I am currently more focused on Backend developer in .NET environments.

Currently working in Vueling by Hiberus Technology.

■ Employment History

.NET Programmer Analyst at Vueling, Zaragoza, Spain

August 2018 - Present

Backend development in projects in the .NET Framework.

Maintenance and support for different versions of platforms.

Development and support of Web Services, ASP.NET Web API.

Generation of technical documentation.

Agile methodologies. Scrum

Management of Git, TFS and VSTS as version control tools.

.NET Programmer Analyst at Hiberus Tecnología, Zaragoza, Spain

July 2018 - Present

Maintenance and support for different versions of platforms.

Development and support of Web Services, ASP.NET Web API.

Generation of technical documentation.

Agile methodologies. Scrum

Management of Git, TFS and VSTS as version control tools.

Software Engineer at Endalia HR Consulting & Software, Zaragoza

December 2016 - July 2018

Technical area oriented to the analysis, design and implementation of information management software.

Education

 ${\tt BsC\,in\,Software\,Engineering,University\,of\,Zaragoza,Zaragoza}$

2012 - 2016

Awards & Honors

Prize for the challenge: "GFT: Change the future of banking" in HackUPC 2016

October 2016

Barcelona

Prize for the challenge: "GFT: Change the future of banking" in HackUPC 2016 (Autumn).

Details

Zaragoza, Spain, (+34) 620938505 raul.piraces@gmail.com

Date / Place of birth

1994-06-02

Ejea de los Caballeros

Nationality

Spanish

Links

Web

Github

Linkedin

Skills

.NET Framework

Javascript

ASP.NET

.NET Core

SQL

Angular Framework

Languages

English

Spanish

First Prize in Keystone Hackaton, "Keyword Search in Big Linked Data"

July 2016

Santiago de Compostela

First Prize in Keystone Hackaton, "Keyword Search in Big Linked Data".

Paper "Process Mining to improve Security in Web Information Systems"

July 2016

Zaragoza

Paper "Process Mining to improve Security in Web Information Systems", sent and accepted at "IV Congreso Nacional de I+D en Defensa y Seguridad (DESEI+D 2016)".

Final Degree Project

July 2016

Zaragoza

Final Degree Project: "Process Mining to improve Security in Web Information Systems", obtaining an evaluation of 9.4 out of 10 with honors.